<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="Bio">Garth Albert Ferguson is a 24-year-old health centre receptionist who enjoys listening to music, bridge and planking. He is smart and inspiring, but can also be very untrustworthy and a bit standoffish. He is an Argentinian Sikh who defines himself as pansexual. He started studying medicine at college but never finished the course. He is a vegan. Physically, Garth is in good shape. He is very tall with chocolate skin,Garth Albert Ferguson is a 24-year-old health centre receptionist who enjoys listening to music, bridge and planking. He is smart and inspiring, but can also be very untrustworthy and a bit standoffish. He is an Argentinian Sikh who defines himself as pansexual. He started studying medicine at college but never finished the course. He is a vegan. Physically, Garth is in good shape. He is very tall with chocolate skin, brown hair and blue eyGarth Albert Ferguson is a 24-year-old health centre receptionist who enjoys listening to music, bridge and planking. He is smart and inspiring, but can also be very untrustworthy and a bit standoffish. He is an Argentinian Sikh who defines himself as pansexual. He started studying medicine at college but never finished the course. He is a vegan. Physically, Garth is in good shape. He is very tall with chocolate skin, brown hair and blue ey brown hair and blue eyes. He grew up in a working class neighbourhood. After his father died when he was young, he was raised by his mother He is currently in a relationship with Levi Harmony Sanders. Levi is 19 years older than him and works as a politician. Garth\'s best friend is a health centre receptionist called Barbara Payne. They get on well most of the time. He also hangs around with Evan Oliver and Michelle Walker. They enjoy vandalising bus stops together. For privacy reasons, your creation will be removed from the web at 12:15pm BST and later deleted from our server, unless you choose to publish it.</string>
</resources>